Found 11 headers:
Line 1130: II. THE RED-HEADED LEAGUE
Line 2166: III. A CASE OF IDENTITY
Line 2917: IV. THE BOSCOMBE VALLEY MYSTERY
Line 3971: V. THE FIVE ORANGE PIPS
Line 4808: VI. THE MAN WITH THE TWISTED LIP
Line 5850: VII. THE ADVENTURE OF THE BLUE CARBUNCLE
Line 6778: VIII. THE ADVENTURE OF THE SPECKLED BAND
Line 7917: IX. THE ADVENTURE OF THE ENGINEERÆS THUMB
Line 8826: X. THE ADVENTURE OF THE NOBLE BACHELOR
Line 9803: XI. THE ADVENTURE OF THE BERYL CORONET
Line 10869: XII. THE ADVENTURE OF THE COPPER BEECHES
